<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security10x News on </title>
    <link>https://security10x.com/tags/security10x-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security10x News on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:40:50 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://security10x.com/tags/security10x-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Android’s accelerometer could be used to eavesdrop on your calls</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/your-androids-accelerometer-could-be-used-to-eavesdrop-on-your-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:40:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/your-androids-accelerometer-could-be-used-to-eavesdrop-on-your-calls/</guid>
      <description>Just because you don’t give an application access to your microphone doesn’t mean that it can’t listen to you. Researchers have created an attack called Spearphone that uses the motion sensors in Android phones to listen to phone calls, interactions with your voice assistant, and more.
When you install an Android app, it has to ask your permission if it wants access to your microphone so that it can listen to what you’re saying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Keep Your Children Safe on Their Smartphones</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/how-to-keep-your-children-safe-on-their-smartphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 23:27:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/how-to-keep-your-children-safe-on-their-smartphones/</guid>
      <description>Are you concerned about what your children are able to access on their smartphones? Cybersecurity expert Matt Boddy explains how you can restrict what they can and can&amp;rsquo;t access.
 The video is from Sophos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability Vlc No Patch</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/critical-vulnerability-vlc-no-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 22:07:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/critical-vulnerability-vlc-no-patch/</guid>
      <description>Germany’s national Computer Emergency Response Team (CERT-Bund) has issued a security advisory to alert users of VLC media player of a severe vulnerability affecting this extremely popular open-source software.
 “A remote, anonymous attacker can exploit the vulnerability in VLC to execute arbitrary code, cause a denial-of-service condition, exfiltrate information, or manipulate files,” said CERT-Bund, which also discovered the security loophole.
 The memory-corruption flaw is known to reside in the player’s latest release, 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four Questions Organisations Need to Ask After a Cyber Attack</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/four-questions-organisations-need-to-ask-after-a-cyber-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 15:58:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/four-questions-organisations-need-to-ask-after-a-cyber-attack/</guid>
      <description>Cyber attacks are inevitable, but it’s how an organisation deals with them that can make or break their business. Have they got all the answers, and do they fully understand the implications? Can they be sure the attack won’t happen again?
 How and where did the security breach take place? What information was accessed? How can systems be recovered quickly? How do you prevent it from happening again?  Read the full story on InformationSecurityBuzz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Signatures in PDFs are Broken</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/digital-signatures-in-pdfs-are-broken/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 15:01:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/digital-signatures-in-pdfs-are-broken/</guid>
      <description>Researchers have demonstrated spoofing of digital signatures in PDF files.
This would matter more if PDF digital signatures were widely used. Still, the researchers have worked with the various companies that make PDF readers to close the vulnerabilities. You should update your software.
Details are here.
Read the full story on Schneier</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Office 365 Site Pushes Trickbot Trojan as Browser Update</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/fake-office-365-site-pushes-trickbot-trojan-as-browser-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 14:36:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/fake-office-365-site-pushes-trickbot-trojan-as-browser-update/</guid>
      <description>Attackers have created a fake Office 365 site that is distributing the TrickBot password-stealing disguised as Chrome and Firefox browser updates.
This fake Office 365 site found by MalwareHunterTeam looks like any site that would normally belong to Microsoft. In fact all of its links point to pages hosted on Microsoft domains.
Read the full story on InformationSecurityBuzz</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoom Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/zoom-vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 14:01:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/zoom-vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>The Zoom conferencing app has a vulnerability that allows someone to remotely take over the computer’s camera.
It’s a bad vulnerability, made worse by the fact that it remains even if you uninstall the Zoom app:
 This vulnerability allows any website to forcibly join a user to a Zoom call, with their video camera activated, without the user’s permission.
 On top of this, this vulnerability would have allowed any webpage to DOS (Denial of Service) a Mac by repeatedly joining a user to an invalid call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rdp Bug Takes New Approach to Host Compromise</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/rdp-bug-takes-new-approach-to-host-compromise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 04:32:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/rdp-bug-takes-new-approach-to-host-compromise/</guid>
      <description>Researchers show how simply connecting to a rogue machine can silently compromise the host.
Most security professionals know they can use Microsoft’s Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) to connect to other machines but may not consider how merely using RDP could compromise one.
A recently discovered RDP vulnerability could silently compromise a host when it connects to a rogue machine, researchers report. CVE-2019-0887, discovered by Eyal Itkin, a vulnerability researcher with Check Point Software Technologies, was classified as Important and patched this month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Growing Threat Targeted Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/the-growing-threat-targeted-ransomware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 11:11:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/the-growing-threat-targeted-ransomware/</guid>
      <description>Ransomware targeting organizations is a growing threat. The extent of that threat is not always obvious.
A new analysis from Symantec (PDF), using its own telemetry, shows the extent of the growth in targeted attacks against organizations over the last two years &amp;ndash; and especially since the beginning of this year.
Read the full story on SecurityWeek</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nvidias Tegra Chipset Attack</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/nvidias-tegra-chipset-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 10:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/nvidias-tegra-chipset-attack/</guid>
      <description>A flaw impacting millions of mobile and internet of things (IoT) devices running NVIDIA’s Tegra processor opens the door for a variety of attacks, including device hijacking or siphoning of data.
The warning comes from researcher Triszka Balázs, who discovered the flaw and asserts that the bug “affects every single Tegra device released so far.” He also created a proof-of-concept (PoC), called Selfblow, to exploit the vulnerability. On Thursday, NVIDIA released a patch for the bug (CVE‑2019‑5680) via a security bulletin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flaw Allows Attackers to Alter Media Files Sent via Whatsapp Telegram</title>
      <link>https://security10x.com/flaw-allows-attackers-to-alter-media-files-sent-via-whatsapp-telegram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 10:05:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://security10x.com/flaw-allows-attackers-to-alter-media-files-sent-via-whatsapp-telegram/</guid>
      <description>Researchers have reported a vulnerability in the Android versions of WhatsApp and Telegram that could allow malicious actors to manipulate media files sent via the apps.
This “media file-jacking” flaw could allow attackers to alter photographs, modify invoices (to aid in a financial scam), swap out files in a particular channel feed, or potentially even manipulate audio messages, warned cyber-software firm Symantec in a July 15 company blog post.
Read the full story on SCMagazine</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>